Nanette Julius

Email: njulius89@gmail.com | Cell: (661) 993-7831 https://linkedin.com/in/nanette-julius/ | https://github.com/njulius89 www.nanettejulius.com

SUMMARY

Creative problem-solving full stack web developer with the coordinating and interpersonal skills to match. I create user friendly, visually appealing applications that are functional and organized. Strong detail, communication and leadership skills developed through teaching experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, Materialize, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, UX/UI Design, React.js, RESTful API, AJAX, Firebase, Photoshop, WordPress, Chrome Dev Tools, GIT, GitHub, Node.js, Express, React Native, Google Firebase, SQL, Handlebars & MongoDB.

EDUCATION

University of California Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

2017

Cal State University Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA B.A. Music

2013

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Swapr

- Full stack app for trading goods with other users nearby. Users can search for items within a set distance and arrange to meet and trade using the integrated chat feature.
- https://swapr-app.herokuapp.com/

EventStay

- A frontend web app routing users to hotels near their desired events. Users can choose
 an event anywhere in the world and find the cheapest, highest rated hotels near it.
- http://nanettejulius.com/EventStay/

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

REX IT Inc. - Pasadena, CA

06/2016 to 07/2017

- Junior Web Developer
 - Designed clean, user-friendly, responsive websites/web applications
 - Ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
 - Developed new user-facing features
 - Helped other engineers with bug fixes and feature development
 - Application testing and improving test coverage

EMPLOYMENT

Gorman Learning Center – Santa Clarita, CA Performing Arts Program Director/ Music Teacher 08/2015 to 06/2017

Heritage Christian School - Granada Hills, CA Elementary Music Teacher/ Chapel Coordinator 07/2014 to 06/2015